footfetishextreme.com 2014-06-25

# Hot Legs And Feet - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**Agreement**

By logging on and using the Site, you agree to and accept our privacy policy. At HOTLEGSANDFEET, we understand that sharing your personal information with us over the internet requires trust. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you that we will protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us through our website (the "Site"). This includes your name, address, phone number, email address, and any other personal information that can be linked to you. We will collect and use information about your preferences and browsing habits to help personalize your experience on the website. We will also use this information to make content purchasing and other decisions, but all such information will be anonymous.

**We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances.**

The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your consent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.

 **Personal Information Collected**

We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when joining the HOTLEGSANDFEET Site. This information includes your email address and a password when you join HOTLEGSANDFEET.  

When you visit HOTLEGSANDFEET, you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit our Site so we can enhance and customize your online experience. You can choose to use HOTLEGSANDFEET without cookies if you wish. To use the website without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)  

When you are logged into your HOTLEGSANDFEET account, your browsing activities are logged into a secure database that helps us create personalized recommendations for you. Our site contains personalization features that collect data from your browsing, viewing and searching activities to provide custom movie and scene recommendations for you and to otherwise personalize your site experience. Some of this information is also used in an anonymized fashion to help us determine what movies we should add to the site and to make other site-wide decisions.

**Third Party Billing Companies**

The third party billing companies which collect your payment for using our services collect personal and billing information that we have access to but do not store. You acknowledge and agree that we do not have any responsibility for the collection, maintenance or safeguarding of the privacy of any such personal or billing information provided to such third party billing companies and that such responsibility is solely between you and the third party billing company. We encourage you to examine and determine your satisfaction with the policies of such third party billing companies prior to your using them.

**When and With Whom We Share Your Personal Information**

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners or sponsors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**How We Protect the Security of Your Personal Information**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures.

**Communications from the Site**

  * **Special Offers and Updates**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.
  *  **Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.
  *  **Service Announcement**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. These communications are not promotional in nature. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we may send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications.
  *  **Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email, in accordance with the users wishes.

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of receiving Special Offers, Updates, and Newsletters. Users who no longer wish to receive emails of this nature, may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the Unsubscribe link included in the emails.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on this page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use HOTLEGSANDFEET, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use HOTLEGSANDFEET after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy.

**Outbound Links**

The Sites may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave HOTLEGSANDFEET they should read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**How to Contact HOTLEGSANDFEET**

If you have comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us through our [support form](http://support.ddfprod.com/?ref=HOTLEGSANDFEET.COM) or via email at support@HOTLEGSANDFEET.COM.
